suresafety.com 2015-09-07

# Sure Safety- Privacy Policy

By using a  **[www.suresafety.com](http://www.suresafety.com/)**   **Internet Site or providing personal information to us, you are consenting to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy and any applicable Country or Web Site Privacy Statements. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Policy, do not use**   **[www.suresafety.com](http://www.suresafety.com/)**   **Internet Site.**

  **Limitations on the Collection, Use and Disclosure of Personal Information**

  To the extent required by applicable law, whenever [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) collects personal information on a [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet Site,[ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) will:  
Provide timely and appropriate notice to you about its data practices.

  Collect, use, disclose and transfer your personal information only with your consent, which  may be express or implied, depending on the sensitivity of the personal information, legal requirements, and other factors.

  Collect your personal information only for specific, limited purposes. The information we collect will be relevant, adequate and not excessive for the purposes for which it is collected.

  Process your personal information in a manner consistent with the purposes for which it was originally collected or to which you have subsequently consented.

  Take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is reliable for its intended use, accurate, complete, and, where necessary, kept up-to-date.

  Not use your personal information for direct marketing purposes without giving you an opportunity to “opt-out”; and Take appropriate measures, by contract or otherwise, to provide adequate protection for personal information that is disclosed to a third party or transferred to another country, including transferswithin  [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/).

  **Security of Personal Information**  
Your personal information will generally be stored in www.suresafety.com databases or databases maintained by our service providers.

[ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) maintains reasonable safeguards to protect the confidentiality, security and integrity of your personal information. For example, we use secure socket layer (SSL) technology to transfer personal information over the Internet. Although we use security measures to help protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure, misuse or alteration, as is the case with all computer networks linked to the Internet, we cannot guarantee the security of information provided over the Internet and will not be responsible for breaches of security beyond our reasonable control.

  **Links to Third Party Internet Sites**  
[**www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet Sites may contain links to Internet sites that are not operated by [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/). These links are provided as a service and do not imply any endorsement of the activities or content of these sites, nor any association with their operators. [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) does not control these Internet sites and is not responsible for their content, security, or privacy practices. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on web sites you visit before using the site or providing personal information.

  **Retention of Personal Information**  
www.suresafety.com retains the personal information collected on www.suresafety.com Internet Sites as long as necessary to provide the services, products and information you request or as permitted by applicable law.

  **Children and Parents**  
[**www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet Sites are generally not intended for persons under 13 years of age. [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) does not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from or about children on its Internet Sites except as permitted under applicable law. If your child has submitted personal information and you would like to request that such information be deleted from our records, you may do so by using the feedback mechanisms provided at a particular contact us page or by writing to [ **onlinestore@suresafety.com**](mailto:onlinestore@suresafety.com).

  **Changes to this Policy and our Privacy Statements**  
[**www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) reserves the right to update or modify this Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our[ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet Sites. We also reserve the right to update or modify our Web Site Privacy Statements, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised Privacy Statement on the applicable [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet Site. If we modify this Policy or any Privacy Statement, the modifications will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Policy or Privacy Statement on the applicable [ **www.suresafety.com**](http://www.suresafety.com/) Internet site.

  **Disclaimer Policy**  
Sure Safety does not promise that the site or any content, service or feature of the site will be error-free or uninterrupted, or that any defects will be corrected, or that your use of the site will provide specific results. The site and its content are delivered as on “AS-IN” and “AS-AVAILABLE” basis. The images, pictures, and illustrations found on this site are for illustration purposes only, and do not necessarily representing the exact products, services, or ideas in the context they are found in. It is the buyer’s responsibility prior to purchase to clarify with the seller exactly what products and services are being provided for to purchase. The information contained in this website is for general information purposes only. All information provided on the site is subject to change without notice. The information is provided by Sure Safety and while we endeavor to keep the information up to date and correct, we make no representations or warranties of any kind, express or implied, about the completeness, accuracy, reliability, suitability or availability with respect to the website or the information, products, services, or related graphics contained on the website for any purpose. Any reliance you place on such information is therefore strictly at your own risk.

Sure Safety in no event will we be liable for any loss or damage including without limitation, indirect or consequential loss or damage, liability or injuries caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction of or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use, whether for breach of contract, tort, negligence or any other cause of action of the use of this website. Please note that such errors, inaccuracies or omissions may relate to pricing, specifications, technical features and availability, and we reserve the right to cancel or refuse to accept any order placed based on incorrect pricing or available information though we regret any inconvenience which may be so caused. 

The site will be free of viruses or contamination or destructive features. Sure Safety disclaims all warranties, express or implied, including any warranties of accuracy, non-infringement, merchantability and fitness for a particular purpose. Disclaims any and all liability for the acts, omissions and conduct of any third parties in connection with or related to your use of the site and/or any Sure Safety Services. You assume total responsibility for your use of the site and any linked sites. Your sole remedy against Sure Safety for dissatisfaction with the site or any content is to stop using the site or any such content. This limitation of relief is a part of the bargain between the parties. 

Any reproduction of material herein without the explicit permission of Sure Safety in writing is prohibited.   
The above disclaimer applies to any damages, liability or injuries caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interruption, deletion, defect, delay in operation or transmission, computer virus, communication line failure, theft or destruction of or unauthorized access to, alteration of, or use, whether for breach of contract, tort, negligence or any other cause of action.
